activehosted.com 2012-06-25

# Privacy Policy

**Introduction  **  
ActiveCampaign respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at ActiveCampaign’s Web site.

**Part I. Information Collection  **  
ActiveCampaign collects information through our Web site at several points. We collect the following information about primary visitors: Contact Forms, Ordering Process, Mailing List, Affiliate Process.

We may also collect usernames and or other forms of identification which our users divulge about other people, such as referrals or gift purchases. ActiveCampaign does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.

We collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information: IP, Referrer, Host, etc.. We collect demographic data in order to provide general statistical information. This does not include personal or sensitive data.

We verify the accuracy of this information through several processes.

We collect this information through contact forms, ordering process, mailing lists, and the affiliate program. The information that is collected is voluntary. To receive our products and services, contact and other information is mandatory because our ordering procedure. Other information we request is optional.

We may employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable ActiveCampaign to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies do have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information.

**Part II. Information Usage.  **  
The information collected by ActiveCampaign will be used for customer service, ordering procedures, and opt-in informational mailings. Users who provide information will receive the certain product, mailing, or service he or she requested.

Registered users will receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

The information we collect may be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history. We will not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources.

We offer links to other Web sites. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.

**Part III. Access to Information  **  
ActiveCampaign maintains the accuracy of our information by frequent up-keep and allowing users to modify their information at any time. Users may access their own personal information and contact us about inaccuracies they may find. Users may also delete their information from our database upon request by e-mailing info@activecampaign.com

**Part IV. Problem Resolution  **  
If problems arise, users may contact ActiveCampaign. We are committed to resolving disputes within 2-3 business days.

**Part V. Data Storage and Security**  
ActiveCampaign protects user information with various security measures.

**Part VI.  U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework **  
ActiveCampaign complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland.  ActiveCampaign has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view ActiveCampaign’s certification, please visit [http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/)

ActiveCampaign has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by ActiveCampaign, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints "http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints") for more information and to file a complaint.

If you have any further questions about privacy or security, please contact us by sending an email to: info@activecampaign.com
